<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<kml xmlns="http://www.opengis.net/kml/2.2" 
  xmlns:ktx="http://www.karunatree.com/kml/ext/2.2">
  

  <Document>
      
    <Camera>
  		<longitude>-109.7682022044922</longitude>
  		<latitude>38.69656556160413</latitude>
  		<altitude>1118.397465993844</altitude>
  		<heading>151.8242721814273</heading>
  		<tilt>40.30685159553708</tilt>
  		<roll>1.772759250744586e-06</roll>
  	</Camera>
  	
  	<ktx:script>
  	  Squinting against the sun, Sam felt the hot breath of the desert ruffling his hair as it funneled into the mouth of the canyon. The wind was the only thing stirring over the landscape at this time of the afternoon. Desert creatures were sensibly withdrawn in burrows and shady hollows waiting for the cool of evening. The periodic tink-tink of a rock hammer echoed off the smooth stone walls. Sam closed his eyes and inhaled deeply, enjoying the mineral smell of the hot rocks and sand. He loved the solitude and mystery of this place.
  	  The sound of the hammering stopped. Sam turned to see his mother bent close to the earth under the shade tent. She was intently inspecting a small patch of ground, her excavation tools and sketchbooks spilling out of her worn green field pack on the ground next to her. She looked up, smiling as she tucked stray wisps of hair behind her ears. “Sammy, would you bring me the narrow brush? I think I’ve got most of the rock cleared away now.” They had been out here since before sunrise, patiently chipping away at sandy rock and sifting through fine dust, searching for something that his Mom would only describe (with a wink) as being worth the effort. Not that Sam minded. There were few things that he loved more than helping his mother with her digs, hunting for buried fossil treasures from a past that sometimes seemed almost too amazing to believe.
  	</ktx:script>
  	
  	<ktx:flyToSpeed>0.1</ktx:flyToSpeed>
  
  	<Placemark>
  		<name>Excavation Site</name>
  		<open>1</open>  		
  		<Point>
  			<coordinates>-109.7641368831581,38.68527824559933,0</coordinates>
  		</Point>
  	</Placemark>
  	
  	<Placemark>
  		<name>Excavation Site 2</name>
  		<open>1</open>
  		<Point>
  			<coordinates>-109.7841368831581,38.68527824559933,0</coordinates>
  		</Point>
  	</Placemark>
  	
	</Document>
</kml>